textureking.com 2018-09-17

# Free » Privacy Policy Textures from TextureKing

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 18, 2018

#### Summary:

We respect the EU’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) and this policy explains how we collect and treat any information you give us. You won’t find any complicated legal terms or long passages of unreadable text. We’ve no desire to trick you into agreeing to something you might later regret.

#### Why we value your privacy

We value your privacy as much as we do our own, so we’re committed to keeping your personal and business information safe. We’re uncomfortable with the information companies, governments, and other organisations keep on file, so we ask for only the bare minimum from our customers. We’ll never use your personal information for any reason other than why you gave it, and we’ll never give anyone access to it unless we’re forced to by law.

#### How we collect information

We ask for contact information including your name and email address on our website so that we can reply to your enquiry. Our website doesn’t use cookies or scripts that were designed to track the websites you visit.

#### What information we hold

When you contact us by email or through our website, we collect your name, email address, phone number, a social media username, and the company you work for, if you’ve given us that.

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Who’s responsible for your information at our company

The website owner is responsible for the security of your information. You can contact them by email at info@textureking.com if you have any concerns about the information we store.

#### How to complain

We take complaints very seriously. If you’ve any reason to complain about the ways we handle your privacy, please contact by email at info@textureking.com

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### Changes to the policy

If we change the contents of this policy, those changes will become effective the moment we publish them on our website.
